Sara Niasati

UX Designer

saraniasati@gmail.com 438-863-1936 LinkedIn Portfolio

PROFILE

Passionate and curious recent graduate with a degree in Cognitive Systems from UBC, and experience as a User Experience Research Assistant. Skilled in intuitive design and finding patterns in cognitive agents interacting with technology. Recently completed a UX Design program at BrainStation and transitioning career from customer service to UX design with a commitment to making a positive impact.

SKILLS

Figma, InVision, POP, Pitch, Miro, Java, Python

EXPERIENCE

Member Experience Representative | YMCA BC

JAN 2022 - Present, VANCOUVER, BC

- Promoted membership and program sales and services while ensuring exemplary customer service and adherence to safety protocols.
- Ensured member satisfaction and safety by overseeing fitness floor and programming, providing support in program areas, and diffusing conflicts through Non-violent Crisis Intervention methodology.
- Recorded and reported on member satisfaction, interest trends, and activities, and assisted with training new staff and volunteers in procedures and practices.

Concierge Advisor | Aritzia

OCT 2022 - DEC 2022, VANCOUVER, BC

- Provided efficient customer service via phone, chat, and email, while multitasking various systems for case coordination and e-commerce support.
- Leveraged problem-solving skills to facilitate retail and e-commerce orders, returns, client inquiries, tailoring solutions, and styling advice.

EDUCATION

BrainStation | Diploma, User Experience Design

SEP 2022 - MAY 2023, VANCOUVER, BC

University of British Columbia | Bachelor of Science, Cognitive Systems

SEP 2019 - JUL 2022, VANCOUVER, BC

- Teaching Assistant for Research Methods in Cognitive Systems -COGS 303
- 2021-2022 Dean's List

PROJECTS

UX Designer | Mindful Moda

MAY 2023, BrainStation

 Designed a mobile app from concept to high fidelity design using design thinking methodologies, agile development practices, and design software.
Resulted in a highly functional and user-friendly app, increasing user engagement and satisfaction.

UX Research Assistant | Beyond the Bulging Binder

OCT 2022, Sensory Perception & Interaction, Research Group, UBC

Conducted literature review and user interviews to identify needs and pain points. Developed user requirements and implemented them into low and high-fidelity mock-ups of a mobile app. Analyzed cognitive walkthrough interviews with users to improve interface design.